We're going to call the Regards Governor Mead Monson Gas for Tuesday December 2, 2021, but I'm going to
put a gift book.
It's going to personal prayer session.
You have one.
Mr. Johnson.
You want to come to go in here?
As you know, we're okay not a straight.
And I mentioned before to some of the city people that we're having an issue with people.
The traffic is horrible.
And the families are having trouble when they're pulling and getting out because they're
fighting and getting hit.
And we have people that have had to cross street in order to obtain particles for the nursing
facility.
And so what we would like to see done is maybe some type of posting of slow down signs or some
light or maybe a crossing to show that people are crossing.
It's really even when we heads our state of surveyors there for DHS and ICFs.
They both commented on that that it is a safety issue.
And so not only for our residents, but for visitors that come.
And so we would ask that something began.
I know that our law enforcement are great.
But there are so and there have so many calls that they cannot, you know, control there.
So what would we just get something to, you know, alert the people to slow down that this is an area where there is people
that are crossing the street and backing out.
And so whatever we can do to assist, we will be glad to do it.
But we just want the safety for the staff, the residents, the residents, families,
visitors and it's getting to be a more busy or time.
And so if you would place consider that with that beach and everyone here.
Is this my I'm a nursing center?
Yes, on a street.
What's the address?
1100.
Do you know what these are?
Stop staff.
Didn't see if it was something we'd do.
Yes.
All right.
So Tyler is our city manager.
He's on top of staff.
If there's something we can do to help out.
And what can be done?
I know we can, this will be back there.
And so the stuff I've extra patrol, why are you just figuring out what we can do to help out.
All right.
Thank you.
Okay, three A, community crisis center up date, Kelsey,
Kelsey, my my ask, can we get, could you give your number to Melissa if you haven't already
just so we can call you back, staff can call her back, yeah, you just want to write down that way
you're not excited on the air recording, so we just, just so staff can get a hold there and say
this is what we're going to do, this is what I'm going to do, thank you, man, thank you.
Okay, Kelsey's not here, so I guess if she shows up, we can go back to it, so we'll skip that
out for now, she shows up for me and then we'll go back to, for A, clean list, what's your proof?
Sorry.
Hi.
So, what's your proof?
I'm sorry.
Hi.
For B, minutes from the November 18, 2025, regular meeting.
What's your proof?
Second.
Forン.
Five, five, fifth, 10.
What's your proof?
Four, C through J.
I feel like their message on thousands of people can fill in some mourn and that says a lot.
About on individually?
Yes, sir.
So, these shall start at C and discuss which one you're on next?
Well, I think that one description will describe all of these.
So these are some archaic ordinances that regulate the whole and dominant farmers.
I don't believe that.
Here goes in the same time.
But apparently at one point we did and we regulated the running of those.
We'll then when they get our rights done, we recommend that when you repeal the fee section of these.
And since we're working on the fee ordinance, that all of these things have come to mind that we feel like we need to get taken care of before we move forward with some of the fee ordinance.
So in looking at this, the all of these ordinances, they are all from the, the generally portion all the way through the fees and the licensure of pool halls and dollar no farmers is each section of ordinance that deals with those.
I don't know if you shall I get the license just to repeal the fee section.
I thought we should just take out everything related to those.
Since we don't have those to regulate, we want to.
I have as if we get a domino parlour.
I'll, I'll deal with it.
We'll rewrite them.
And there are.
our additional similar ordinances to these that are paid and things like that.
I just felt like there would be a lot to put all of them on one careful meeting.
Thank you.
Okay.
Any other questions for Mr. Ngui?
We get relevant.
So, for C, ordinance 2025,
2500, 2019, and a 2016, Rebellion Section 12,
80, mm-hmm.
Most of your brief seconds.
Hi.
Thank you.
My for Connect.
4D, ordinance 2025, 2017, Rebellion Section 12,
82, Miss.
What's your proof?
Okay.
8, 10, sorry.
10, 10, 10.
Hi.
Хіーー k.
4E, Orderness 2025, NAS 18 Rebellion Section 12,
Then, 12-96.
Oh, should do good.
Yes, yes.
double.
All right.
4F.
Or an 12.5-19.
Or a 12-97.
Oh, it's two of three.
Second.
All right.
4G.
Or an 12-20.
Or an 20.5-20.
Or a 12-19.
12-98.
Eight.
There's two proof.
The next.
All right.
I.
Five.
Four.
Eight.
Two.
Five.
I.
Four.
Five.
Motion to group.
Second.
Double.
Aye.
E7.
Jones.
Aye.
Barrett.
Four.
Jay.
Order.
Twenty.
Five.
Four.
Double.
E7.
Jones.
Head.
Five.
Four.
Jay.
Order.
Twenty.
Five.
Nine.
Jones.
Barrett.
Epstein.
E7.
Six.
Other.
New business.
As residents.
Posting this agenda.
Seven.
Staff reports.
Eight.
Mayor.
Council.
Community.
Announcements.
That's what I want to say thanks to all your crews for downtown.
I've got so many messages about how pretty it looks and how nice it looks.
And you guys got us ready for the tree lighting on that, about your folks.
The tree lighting on Friday, on the Friday, on Saturday, but I just want to tell you, I appreciate
your efforts.
There are a lot of messages about how I get it looked, so I know it takes away from
other stuff you're doing, but we appreciate it very much.
City manager's medication, just to remind everybody, I have like four things.
I remind everybody of the tree lighting at six, five, I think I'm going to see it.
I mean, Friday night and then we have the parade Saturday night at six, and then it's all right.
If it's on my calendar sometimes it's not really numbered.
So we have that and then really positive, really exciting news.
We were told today that we've been awarded the obelisk grant.
So you know we went after the main street grant for, you know, something that I thought would be really cool.
I think back when Kevin was driving the bus, there were three, three, one in the day and it was actually all the main.
Is that less or not there?
He ran over.
Hey, and so we're not going to put it up here in front of security.
You won't be in front of the room anymore, so it'll be really cool.
I love you, Tyler.
Thank you, Kevin.
And then, so we have that and then I ask her still to give us an update.
So you know how a few menus, we kind of had some questions about our 501C3s, how we want.
So I reached up to the auditors, personal and send you over there.
So I ask her still to kind of update everybody on that and everything.
So.
So when we don't know when it's a radio, how we're talking about it, it's like that being said,
but we do have to manage.
And it was interesting talking to Frank Crawford.
I've covered in associate, you know, he was saying more and more
cities are doing this because they're always looking for revenues.
So, you know, because revenue is so tight.
So...
So, that's the role of Crawford Pills.
That's the role of Bill.
And the last thing I have is we have a new employee back there.
I don't know if Cindy wants to introduce her.
She's sent you two going out.
Rogers, and she's on the right side.
Ooh!
A bleak, populace, again.
Explain what that is a little bit because I was not around back then when it was here.
But from the pictures, it was a project that was designed before I came here.
But I always thought it would be a cool project.
So, what it is, it's like a sphere that has, like, the distance is just two different towns on different sides of it.
So, you know, back in the old days when you come up through it, and it's like,
110 miles, 90 miles, or whatever.
Yeah.
No, it does not spin around.
Don't look at me.
I didn't run over it.
He says back the old days that you remember being,
No, I don't.
So, I guess, trying to be a creep up on wrongly,
used to set it in the middle of maintenance, Central.
I was about to study the business.
Go to the fourth.
So, the Charlie on tracks.
When the Charlie on tracks, how did it deviate from its tracks?
I was going to say, the driver was in the trouble.
So, it's a deal.
Yeah, it's a D.R.I mean Google, you know.
Wow, that's getting you guys.
I think it would be another attraction, you know, it's like, we're bringing it to your brain and
revenue, so I mean, nope.
You got it.
There was a small picture of it floating around up there.
I didn't see the word.
I just have to tell you, I'm all the more.
I know we were looking for some of those to replicate the content.
I think we found three sides maybe.
So that's the right.
I didn't see all four sides.
I didn't see the one up at downstream.
It's right there where the three states meet.
Oh, yeah.
Let's see that.
Yeah.
That's what that means.
But that one's like plus the ground, right?
Yeah, yeah.
There's a tall B.
Oh, it's tall.
Right?
How tall?
You want it downstream used to be tall.
Yeah.
But I mean, they're like, can't be taller, nothing?
Oh, yeah.
So this is this ising an apple of warm.
Okay.
So we're going to have a light.
I'll take a look before that.
So we probably shouldn't talk about that, but I don't know.
It's a bridge.
What do you mean?
All right.
Number two.
This meeting will be.
Continues.
The gas chambers reach me in the staff room for the purposes of executive session.
That the completion of the regular meeting.
And the M.I.P.F.A.
Me.